Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of Geographic Images circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: New York City Views - Brooklyn, 185271
  - Subseries IIIB: BROOKLYN - FLAT MATERIAL
    - Brooklyn - Flat Material -Views
      - General Views - Prints (Folder FF470)
        "City of Brooklyn, L.I. taken from Rush Street," drawn by John Bornet, printed by A. Weingartner, 1855
        "View of Brooklyn, L.I. from U.S. Hotel, New York," drawn by E. Whitefield, printed by F. Michelin, 1846
        "View of Williamsburgh, L.I. from Grand St. N.Y.," drawn by E. Whitefield, lithograph of Endicott and Co., 1852
        "Manhattan Beach," Sackett and Wilhelms Litho. Co.
        "Equestrian Institute, No. 61 South Fourth Street, East Brooklyn. Geo. W. Walker and Co., proprietors," lithograph of T. Bonar [interior view, men and women on horseback].
        "Union Pond, Williamsburgh, L.I.," lithograph by Thomas and Eno. {men and women ice skating].
      - Aerial Views - Photos (Folder FF471)
        Fulton Street and Borough Hall
        Fulton Street circa 1908
        Fulton Street from Temple Bar
        Fulton Street from Chapman's Dry Goods Store
        Atlantic and Flatbush Aves., 1903
        Aerial View of Red Hook, by Fairchild Aerial Surveys
        Rooftop view, looking north east to Brooklyn Bridge
        Looking west from tower of the Troop C Armory [Brooklyn Museum visible], circa 1900
        Atlantic Avenue from Nostrand Avenue [train tracks and 23rd Regiment Armory visible]
      - Street Views - Photos (Folder FF472)
        Fort Hamilton and surrounding shoreline [4 images]
        Grand View Hotel in Fort Hamilton, 1888
        Brooklyn Mercantile Library, Montague Street
        Remsen Street, west from Court Street
        Washington Avenue, 1914, photo by Roege
        Fulton Street, corner of Flatbush Avenue, 1917
        Nevins Street between Flatbush Avenue and Livingston Street, 1917, photo by Roege
        Nostrand Avenue at Gates Avenue, 1917, photo by Roege
        Brooklyn Navy Yard with piles of ammunition, Brooklyn Bridge under construction in background
        Highland Boulevard [house on a plateau]
        Flatbush Avenue and Grand Army Plaza (2 views)
        State Street, photo by George Hall
        503 Fulton Street
        Greenpoint (2 images)
        Bensonhurst shoreline, with boats
        Clinton Avenue
        1 Jamaica Avenue, Railroad Men's Building, showing Brooklyn-Manhattan Transit War Memorial, 1923
        Broadway and Second Street, Williamsburgh, featuring Dime Savings Bank building
        24 Myrtle Ave, in front of E. R. Gillespie's Book Store [3 copies], handwritten note on back says the figure in front of bookstore is Wilberforce Eames
        Williamsburgh (6 views)
        Unidentified (2 views)
      - Views - Cemeteries (Folder FF473)
        Greenwood Cemetery - "Monument of the New York City Fire Department," drawn by R. Trembly, printed by Nagel and Weingartener, 1849. [3 versions of the same print]
      - Views - Coney Island (Folder FF474)
        Coney Island shoreline (3 photos)
        Hotel Shelburne, 1921, photo by Roege
        Manhattan Beach Hotel
        Brighton Beach Hotel, atop 120 railcars so it could be moved inland, 1888
        Aerial view of Coney Island, circa 1892 [Elephantine Colossus a.k.a. the Elephant Hotel]
        Bathers by the Iron Pier, circa 1890s
        Aerial View of Sea Beach Palace
        "On the Beach at Coney Island on a Hot Day in August," photo by Pictorial News Co.
        "Summer Scenes at Coney Island," tearsheet from the Daily Graphic, July 3, 1877. [collage of images of Coney Island hotels, with an inset map of the New York and Manhattan Beach Railroad lines]
      - Views - Parks (Folder FF475)
        Fort Greene Park, The Prison Ship Martyrs' Monument
        Prospect Park, James S.T. Stranahan monument
        Prospect Park, Nethermead Arches
        Prospect Park, Endale Arch
        Prospect Park, photo by TE Davis, circa 1950.
    - Brooklyn - Flat Material - Buildings
      - Churches (Folder FF476)
        Holy Cross Church (Father Wood's Church), Church Avenue
        Holy Trinity Church, Brooklyn Heights (interior)
        Flatbush Dutch Reformed Church, corner of Flatbush and Church Avenues, 1903
        Church of the Messiah and Incarnation, 80 Greene Avenue
        Simpson Methodist Episcopal Church, Clermont Avenue and Willoughby Street, photo by George P. Hall and Son, 1895
        Simpson Methodist Episcopal Church, Clermont Avenue and Willoughby Street, Hayward and Lepine, lithographers, 1867
        Church of the Holy Trinity, Brooklyn Heights, F. and S. Palmer, lithographers, 1845 (2 copies)
        Washington Avenue Baptist Church, Sarony, Knapp and Major, lithographers
        St. John's Church, Bedford Avenue, Major and Knapp, lithographers
        Designs for the New Plymouth Church (Rev. H. W. Beecher's), Brooklyn
        2 photos of unidentified churches.
      - Clubs and Organizations (Folder FF477)
        Naval Branch YMCA, Sands Street, photo by Goodell
        Midwood Club, East 21st Street
        Elks Lodge, 110 Livingston Street (later Board of Education headquarters)
        Montauk Club, 25 Eighth Avenue, photo by F.E. Parshley.
      - Government (Folder FF478)
        City Hall, Brooklyn [print] (now Borough Hall)
        City Hall Brooklyn draped in mourning for the death of President Lincoln [photo] (now Borough Hall)
        County Court House, "Waiting for the Verdict,- Theodore Tilton vs. Rev. Henry Ward Beecher," photo by Salomo and Co., 1875
      - Institutions (Folder FF479)
        Brooklyn Orphan Asylum Society, Atlantic Avenue, Bedford-Stuyvesant.
      - Manufactories and Warehouses (Folder FF480)
        Brooklyn City Flour Mills, Fulton and Furman Streets, 1876
        New York Pier and Warehouse Co., plan of piers and warehouses, designed by J. Burrows Hyde, drawn by J. Heuvelman, 1870.
        River View of Iron Piers and Warehouses, designed by J. Burrows Hyde, drawn by J. Heuvelman, 1870.
        I.S. Remson Manufacturing Company, Grand Street
        L. Waterbury & Co. Cordage and Bagging, Ten Eyck Street
        G. H. Johnson & Co. grain warehouse
      - Residences A-M (Folder FF481)
        Bergen Homestead, East 72nd Street, photo by Nash, 1905
        Bennett House, Shore Road near 74th Street, Bay Ridge
        Birdsall, J. House, Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Cortelyou House, (Old Stone House), Fifth Ave. and 3rd Street, 2 photos by P. Hurly, late 1860s
        Cortelyou House (Old Stone House), Fifth Ave. and 3rd Street, lithographer and publisher N. Currier (2 versions)
        Crooke-Schenck House, or Jan Martense Schenck House, built in 1675, located at 2133 East 63rd Street in Flatlands when it was moved to Brooklyn Museum in 1952. photo by Nash, 1905
        Cutting House, East 17th Street, Flatbush
        De Hart, Simon Aertsen House, still standing on the Gowanus Bay in 1867. Hayward and Co., lithographers
        Ditmas, Henry S. House, Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Ditmas, John House, Flatbush Avenue, photos by Nash, 1903 (2 views)
        Ford, Gordon L. House, 97 Clark Street (interiors) ca. 1896-1897
        Hicks-Platt House, a.k.a. Van Sicklen House or Lady Moody House, 27 Gravesend Neck Road, photoby Nash, 1903
        Lefferts-Laidlaw House, 136 Clinton Avenue, and Henry and Susan McDonald House, 128 Clinton Avenue (both landmarked)
        Lefferts Homestead, Flatbush Avenue, (later moved to Prospect Park), photo by Nash, 1903
        Lott, Albert House, Canarsie Lane, photo by Nash, 1905.
      - Residences N-Z (Folder FF482)
        Ommans, Johannes House 1905
        Remsen House
        Schenck, Nicholas House, Canarsie (now at Brooklyn Museum), photo by Nash, 1903
        Snedeker, Jacob House, New Lots Road, 2 photos by Nash, 1903 and 1905
        Stoothoff and Williamson House, 1587 East 53rd Street (2 photos)
        Striker House, 2243 Church Avenue, photo by Nash, 1905
        Stryker-Williamson House, Gravesend, photo by Nash, 1903
        Van Buren Homestead, a.k.a. Duryea House, Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Vanderbilt, Gertrude Lefferts House, Flatbush Avenue and Lincoln Road
        Vanderbilt, Jeremiah House, 610 Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Vanderveer, J.C. House, Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Vanderveer, J.C. House, water pump, Flatbush Avenue, photo by Nash, 1903
        Vanderveer's Mill, Canarsie, photo by Nash, 1904
        Van Siclen House, New Lots Road, photo by Nash, 1903
        Van Sinderen House, New Lots Road, photo by Nash, circa 1904
        Van Wyck-Hegeman House, Flatlands, photo by Nash, 1903
        Voorhies House, Gravesend Neck Road 1903
        Williamson-Rapelje House, a.k.a. Magee House, New Lots Road, photo by Nash, 1903.
        Willink, John A. House, "Bloemen Heuvel," lithograph by George Hayward
        Wyckoff, John A. House,Flatlands, photo by Nash, 1903
      - Residences - Low Mansion, 3 Pierrepont Place (Folder FF483)
        3 Pierrepont Place, including interiors
      - Schools (Folder FF479)
        Erasmus Hall, 1903.
        Professor Lockwood's Academy, South Oxford Street, 1870.
      - Sports Stadia (Folder FF484)
        Ebbets Field, exterior photo by Hassler
        Ebbets Field, playing field during a game against the Milwaukee Braves, from the New York Herald Tribune, May 2, 1955.
        "Grand Baseball Match for the Championship, between the Excelsior and Atlantic Clubs of Brooklyn," newspaper clipping, 1860
    - Brooklyn - Flat Material - Events
      - Events (Folder FF485)
        Brooklyn Sanitary Fair, 2 lithographs by Brown and Co., 1864
        Brooklyn Trolley Strike, 2 photos by Pach Bros., 1895
        Concert, Brooklyn Academy of Music, 1890
        Fire at 25 Paidge Avenue, Sept 24, 1970
        Grand Temperance Encampment Held at Bushwick, L.I., engraving, 1846
        Military Mass, Brooklyn Navy Yard
        Sunday School Parade, [possibly Prospect Park]
    - Brooklyn -Flat Material - Transportation
      - Plan of Proposed Brooklyn Terminal Station (Folder FF486)
        Nine drawings of a proposed plan for a Brooklyn Terminal Station. Some are signed by McLean, Architect, and dated 1892-1893.
      - Elevated and Surface Railroads (Folder FF487)
        includes photos of:
        Brooklyn Elevated Railroad both during and after construction
        Brighton Beach and West End line Street Railroad, including a panoramic shot of the Bensonhurst Station circa 1870s
        Brooklyn Rapid Transit street cars
        also includes an image of the June 25, 1923 elevated train derailment at Flatbush Avenue and Atlantic Avenue.
  - Subseries IIIC: BROOKLYN OVERSIZE MATERIAL
    - Church of the Holy Trinity, Brooklyn Heights, F & S. Palmer, lithographers, 1846 (Folder OS FF 522)
    - Brooklyn, L.I. as seen from Trinity Church, New York, lithograph by Smith Bros., after a painting by John William Hill, 1853 (Folder OS FF 522)
    - Brooklyn N.Y. 1854, B.F. Smith, delineator, engraved by Wellstood & Peters, published by H. Fern and Co. (Folder OS FF 522)
    - Continental Works, Green Point, Brooklyn, Endicott & Co., Lithographers, circa 1865 (Folder OS FF 522)
    - Manhattan Beach Hotel, photograph, circa 1910 (Folder OS FF 522)
- Series IV: New York City Views - Queens, 185690
  Series IV New York City Views - Queens is arranged in an organizational structure by topic of the view. GENERAL views include aerial views (those taken from airplanes or from the top of a tall building) and birds-eye views (generally 19th-century prints).
  - Subseries IVA: QUEENS - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Queens - Boxed Material - General Views, 185692
      - General Views, 185720 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Queens Lamp Posts, 1934, 185721 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Queens - Boxed Material - Neighborhoods, 185693
      - Arverne, 185722 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Astoria-General, 185723 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Astoria-Residences-A-Z and unidentified, 185726 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Astoria-Residences-Barclay Place, 185727 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Astoria-Residences-Steinway Mansion, 185730 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Astoria-Residences-Sunswick, 185731 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Bayside, 185695 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Bellerose, 185696 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - College Point, 185697 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Corona, 185698 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Elmhurst, 185699 (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Flushing-General, 185737 (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Flushing-Main Street, 185738 (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Flushing-Churches-General, 185741 (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Flushing-Churches-Friends Meeting House, 185742 (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Flushing-Residences-A - Z, 185744 (Box 1, Folder 18)
      - Flushing-Residences-Bowne House, 185745 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Flushing- Residences- Cadwallader Colden House, 185746 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Flushing-Residences-Duryea (Sprong) House, 185747 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Flushing-Schools and Colleges, 185748 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Forest Hills, 185701 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Hollis, 214347 (Box 2, Folder 5.5)
      - Howard Beach, 185751 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Jackson Heights, 185703 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Jamaica, 185704 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Kew Gardens, 185705 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Long Island City, 185706 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Maspeth, 185707 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Newtown, 185708 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - North Beach, 185759 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Ozone Park, 185760 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Rockaway, 185761 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - St. Albans, 185762 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Whitestone, 185763 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous Buildings, 185764 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Queens - Boxed Material - Events, 185715
      - Blizzard of 1888, 185765 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - 1939-1940 World's Fair, 185766 (Box 3, Folder 2-6)
      - 1964-1965 World's Fair, 185771 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Events, 185772 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Queens - Boxed Material - Transportation, 185716
      - LaGuardia Airport, 185773 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Subseries IVB: QUEENS - FLAT MATERIAL
    - Astoria/Ravenswood (Folder FF488)
      View of Astoria, L.I. from the New York Side, lithograph by Currier and Ives, F. Palmer, delineator, 1862
      St. Thomas Chapel, Ravenswood L.I., Attached to St. George's Church, Astoria, lithograph of G. and W. Endicott, circa 1844 (2 copies)
      Delafield Mansion, "Sunswick," photograph by Holmes, 1878
      Ravenswood Classical English Boarding and Day School, photograph, 1872
      unidentified building, Ravenswood-Astoria, L.I., East River, photograph.
    - Bayside (Folder FF489)
      Bayside Park, 3rd Ward, Borough of Queens. Property of North Shore Realty Co. [2 posters advertising the neighborhood.]
    - College Point (Folder FF490)
      College Point, near Flushing, lithograph by Endicott, 1837
      Poppenhusen Residence, College Point, 1872 (photo)
      Poppenhusen Hard Rubber Factory, photo by M. Stadtfeld
      View from Mr. Schleicher's House, East, photo by M. Stadtfeld
      View from Mr. Schleicher's House, South, photo by M. Stadtfeld
      Unidentified House, photo by M. Stadtfeld
    - Flushing (Folder FF491)
      St. George's Church, Flushing, L.I., drawn by H. Dudley, lithograph by Geo. E. Leefe
      The Flushing Oaks, Long Island, drawn by T.K. Wharton, T. Moore's Lithography
      Cedar Grove Cemetery, advertising poster
      Dureyea House, photograph by Nash, 1903
      St. George's Church, photograph by Nash, 1903
      Friends Meeting House, photograph by Nash, 1903
      Prince Homestead, photograph by Nash, 1903
      Garretson House, Main Street, photograph by Nash, 1903
      Bowne House, photograph by Nash, 1903
      Bowne House, photograph by State Photo News Service, Inc., 1939
    - Hollis/Jamaica (Folder FF492)
      Hollis Hotel, photo by Nash, 1905
      Jamaica Town Hall
      King Manor House, photo by Nash, 1903
      Pettit's Hotel, Fulton Street (now Jamaica Avenue), photo by Nash, 1905
      Larramore Titus (?) House, photo by Nash, 1903
      TWA Terminal at Kennedy Airport
    - Long Island City/Newtown/Sunnyside (Folder FF493)
      3 aerial views of Long Island City by Fairchild Aerial Surveys, Inc.
      Brewster Carriage Co. Building, Long Island City
      Payntar House, Jackson and Skillman Avenues, Long Island City, photo by George W. Nash, 1903
      Perry House, Broadway and Elmhurst, Newtown, photo by Nash, 1906
      First Presbyterian Church of Newtown, photo by Nash, 1906
      46th-Bliss Street IRT Station, Sunnyside, photo by Wayne Geist, 1985
    - Rockaways (Folder FF494)
      Marine Pavilion, Rockaway, L.I., lithograph of Pendleton, New York
      Woodsburgh House, Rockaway, L.I.
      [Bird's Eye View of the Rockaways and Jamaica Bay], lithograph by O.H. Bailey
      Far Rockaway, Long Island, N.Y., (bird's eye view of Rockaway, with inset images of buildings), lithograph by O.H. Bailey, 1902
      Edgemere Railroad Station, photo circa 1890
    - Woodhaven (Folder FF495)
      1 photograph of damage and debris from a tornado that struck Woodhaven in July 1895, photo by Mauri's Photo Studio, Ozone Park.
- Series V: New York City Views - Staten Island, 185774
  Series V New York City Views - Staten Island is arranged in an organizational structure by topic of the view. GENERAL views include aerial views (those taken from airplanes or from the top of a tall building) and birds-eye views (generally 19th-century prints).
  - Subseries VA: STATEN ISLAND - BOXED MATERIAL
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Views, 185775
      - Aerial views, 185780 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Beach views, 185784 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Happy Land Amusement Park, South Beach, 185785 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Views of the Harbor, Bay, and Narrows- Prints, 185783 (Box 1, Folder 4)
        includes mid-19th century engravings and lithographs, including views by W.H. Bartlett.
      - Views of the Harbor, Bay and Narrows- photos, 185782 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - General views, 185781 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Buildings, 185777
      - Buildings-General, 185793 (Box 1, Folder 7)
        includes hospitals, schools, government buildings, hotels,and warehouses
      - Churches, 185786 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Residences-A - E, 185788 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Residences-Billopp House,Tottenville, 185789 (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Residences-F - P, 185790 (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Residences-Q - Z, 185791 (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Restoration-Historic Richmond town, 185792 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Staten Island - Boxed Material - Transportation, 185778
      - Transportation, 185794 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Subseries VB: STATEN ISLAND - FLAT MATERIAL
    - General Views - Prints (Folder FF496)
      Encampment of Company A - Tompkins Blues - Capt. John Mayher, at Fort Tompkins, Staten Island, Aug. 20th, 1842, lithograph by Thayer and Co., published by James L. Hewitt.
      Richmond Seminary, Staten Island, N.Y., lithograph by F. & S. Palmer, circa 1847-1848
      The Narrows and Part of Staten Island, lithograph by Deroy, after a drawing by Aug. Kollner, 1850
      View of the New York Quarantine, Staten Island, lithograph by Hayward, 1851
      View of the Marine Hospital and Quarantine Grounds, Staten Island, New York, lithograph by Gustav Wenige, printed by Brown and Quinlan, 1854
      View of the Quarantine Grounds and Buildings, Staten Island, lithograph by G. Hayward, 1858 (3 copies)
      Caprera Hotel and Garden, Clifton, Staten Island, photogravure, circa 1890
      Tottenville, Borough of Richmond, New York, G.H. Bailey, 1902 (photoreproduction)
      Tottenville
      Encampment of Company A – Tompkins Blues – Capt. John Mayher, at Fort Tompkins, Aug. 20, 1842
    - General Views - Photographs (Folder FF497)
      The Old Mill, Fresh Kills Meadow, Richmond, circa 1900
      U.S. Coast Guard Station, Staten Island, photograph by Marilyn Schwartz, 1978
      Richmond Iron Mining Company, Staten Island, 2 photographs of workers by F. L. Huff, circa 1880
      New York Bay from Staten Island, panoramic photograph by A. Loeffler, 1897
    - Buildings (Folder FF498)
      Billop House, a.k.a. the Conference House, (2 photographs)
      Britton Cottage, a.k.a Cubberly House
      Comstock, D.A. House, "Rose Bank," New Brighton, 3 views, lithograph by William Endicott and Co., G.M. Root, delineator
      Cortelyou, Aaron Homestead, a.k.a. Lake or Gifford House
      Dongan, Thomas House (colonial governor of New York, later Earl of Limerick)
      Guyon-Clark House, 360 Guyon Avenue, photograph by E. Wenzel
      Kreuzer-Pelton House, 1262 Richmond Terrace
      Lake-Tysen House
      Ward, W.G., "Oneata," 1867
    - Clippings (Folder FF499)
      Clippings from "The Staten Islander" 1901-1905.
- Series VI: American Views (includes New York State), 50412
  Series II. American Views is arranged alphabetically by state. Within states, views of cities are also arranged alphabetically. In the boxed views, if five or more views of a city exist, that city received its own folder. Within each city, additional folders were also created for buildings, etc. with five or more views.
  - Subseries VIA: AMERICAN VIEWS - BOXED MATERIAL, 185623
    - Alabama, 186270 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Alaska-Captain Amundsen and related, 186281 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Alaska-Cities and buildings, 186282 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Alaska-Nome, 186284 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Alaska-Occupational scenes, 186286 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Alaska-Portraits, 186287 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alaska-Scenery, 186288 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Alaska-Miscellaneous, 186290 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Arizona-Desert Scenes, 186292 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Arizona-Grand Canyon, 186293 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Arizona-Miscellaneous, 186294 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Arkansas, 186295 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - California- A-L, 186296 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - California-Los Angeles, 186297 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - California-M-T, 186298 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - California-Monterey, 186299 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - California-Sacramento, 186300 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - California-San Francisco-General views (excluding photos), 186302 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - California-San Francisco-General Views-photographs, 186303 (Box 2, Folder 2-4)
    - California-San Francisco-Chinatown, 186306 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - California-San Francisco-Earthquake and fire, 186307 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - California-Yosemite, 186308 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - California-Miscellaneous, 186309 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Colorado-Clear Creek and Cripple Creek, 186327 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Colorado-Colorado Springs, 186328 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Colorado-Creede, 186329 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Colorado-Denver, 186330 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Colorado-Leadville, 186331 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Colorado-Manitou Springs/Garden of the Gods, 186333 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Colorado-Pike's Peak, 186335 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Colorado-Railroads, 186336 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Colorado-Scenery, 186338 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Colorado-Miscellaneous, 186339 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut-A-F, 186360 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Connecticut-Bridgeport, 186362 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Connecticut-Fairfield, 186363 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Connecticut-Farmington, 186365 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut-G-L, 186366 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Connecticut-Greenwich, 186367 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Connecticut-Hartford, 186369 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Connecticut-M-Q, 186370 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Connecticut-Middletown, 186372 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Connecticut-Milford, 186373 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Connecticut-New Haven-General views, 186374 (Box 4, Folder 11)